So hello guys, we are back in another new video.
So look, in this video we are going to talk
about some such stocks
which if you buy, if
you want to hold them for at least 10 days or 15 days, then I am going to
tell you about such stocks in today's video.
Overall, in this video I am going to
tell you about momentum stocks, if
you hold them for a little short term,
then you can get very good returns of 5 to 10 percent from
here very
easily. Okay, so we are going to
discuss about such stocks, so let's
start the video directly. Look, first of all,
if we talk about
Indust Tower, okay, if we talk about Indust Tower, then
today you
can see the
returns of 8.26 percent on that stock,
which is a very good
thing. Okay, if we
go a little towards the long term, then if we
talk about one month, okay, then it is very
good.  Returns and one year are
seeing very good returns.
If we talk about the present, then this
company is performing very well at the moment.
If we
talk about its region and its target
and stop loss, then
how its price can go, okay, so
here you can know from the news that
its price can
go very high like a rocket, okay, there are many
such brokers, they have
said here, okay, this is a stock, and if we
talk about its prices, then it is being
told here that its
price is currently 315, its
current price is being seen moving here,
okay, right now its price is being seen moving here, its price is being told
here, it is being told
that its price is 400, there are
chances of it going here
and if we talk about stop loss, then
you can say at 295 or
You can place a stop loss at 300. A small
stop loss is fine and
you can keep a target of 400 within 5 to 10 days. So if you
look at the overall picture, this company is seen to be in a very
bullish trend here
and
this stock has seen very good returns today as well as in the last one week.
If we talk about the next one, then it is
related to insurance.
If we talk about this insurance company, you can see today's performance.
It
opens with a huge gap up from the previous close. After that, again in the
same range and after that, the
market was seen moving in a consolidated area today.
If we talk about its returns, then it was
seen moving around 1,
okay, more than 1 and you
can see the returns that today we are seeing returns of 80 to 0.80. We are
seeing a very good return. If we
talk about one month, then a
little bit  If we look at the negative one year, then this
company is giving very good returns. So,
if we talk about this company, the name of this company is
ICICI.
ICICI Loman Brothers, Loman Brothers, and
Jan General Insurance,
so you can understand about such insurance companies
related to this. So, if we
talk about it,
how can you set its target? So, if we
talk about it, then its new target is being
told here, its price.
Well, if we talk about the price, then it is 1600.
If we talk about some of its things here, then it should be
told here that its
price can go up to 2000. It is being
said so, so if you
look at the overall picture, then it closed at 1684 on 28th March,
and its
value from here is 2000.  Chances are being told,
okay, I am not saying par here, there are
many brokers, they are telling par here, they are
coming to NI also, so
definitely you
can keep this stock in mind, okay,
its price is currently
1700, you can see it, okay,
and its price is being
told here, chances of it going to 2000,
stop loss is not mentioned here, but you should
definitely keep a little stop
loss, okay, you can keep the stop loss
around 1650 or 1600,
okay, even at a big downfall, do
not keep the stop loss here, okay, so if we look at it overall,
this company can look very good in a
few days or
within a few months, okay, so if we
talk about the next, okay, then it is
Indian Hotels, if we talk about it, then this
company is related to Tata, okay, this
company related to Tata works,
Indian Hotels, okay  If you can
see its returns, you can see that 1.73 means
very impressive
returns have been seen today. It
opens with a huge gap up from the closing price, then
consolidates, then after a little down, it becomes
very bullish again, then down again, then
bullish again. So, in this way, you have
seen gap up around the opening, that is,
look, you can see the returns that it
gave around 2 points today.
If we talk about one month or one year, then
you can see the returns that this
company has given a very impressive return. It is a
mid-cap company of 84000 crores. So, if we
look at the overall picture, okay, if we talk about its price, then
it is currently running,
its price is 601, that
means its price was seen running, if we see its price moving, let's
talk a little about its stop loss and target here.
okay, Motilal Oswal, who is a
very big trader of India,
okay, he  Also here, Parse has
said that there is a bullish sentiment on this company and it is
advised to take a position from a two-three day perspective. Okay, it is being said to
hold Parse here for two-three days.
Okay, so let's
talk about some news updates related to this here. Okay, so let's
open it a little bit. If we
talk about its target,
its price is currently seen moving towards 600
and Parse has said here that its
price can be seen going towards 620. Okay,
its price can be seen going towards 620
within two-three days. Okay, so
you can keep this in your mind for a little while.
If you
want to do some trading on it here, then Okay, so if you
look at the overall picture, this company is worth
85000 crores and its
market cap is 85000 crores. And if we
look at the fundamentals, Okay, then the fundamentals of this company are also very
strong.  It is a
stock related company, okay, so which companies have
I told you about, okay, so I
told you about the news, okay, about
Indust Tower, related to ICICI and
Indian Hotel, okay, so
related to that, I have
told the target and stop loss here in this video, so
you can definitely keep this stock in mind,
okay, so guys,
how did you like this video, do
tell us in the comment section and keep liking and subscribing, if you are
new to the channel then guys, we will meet
in the next video with next level
knowledge, till then Jai Hind